All right, we've come to the end of the
deployment section. You'll notice it was
a much shorter section, but I wanted to
explain a little bit of why I chose the
services I chose for hosting. Um, you
can see that this is this is the results
of a survey in 2024 called the state of
JavaScript. And they sent this survey
out to anyone who is a JavaScript
developer. And they responded, which of
these services have you used to host
JavaScript apps? And these are the
responses. And as you can see, AWS is
the number one response. You'll notice I
did not cover that in the videos, and
that is because AWS is not free. If you
want to host on AWS, you do have to give
them your uh you do have to give them a
card number to pay. Um but and AWS can
be a whole course unto itself. Um the
next one, Versell, we did cover. The
next one, GitHub pages, we covered. The
next one, Netlefi, we covered. And the
next one, Cloudflare, we covered. And so
with that you can see that we have taken
in um the top three uh four sorry the
top four aside from AWS hosting
locations. So hopefully that gives you a
good idea and you'll notice that most of
those were pretty similar. So hopefully
it gives you a really good idea of what
you'd need to do going forward to deploy
on any of the other hosting platforms.
Um some that I've heard really good
things about are like render. I have a
service running on render right now. Um
fly.io IO um
is also really easy to use from what
I've heard. Railway also works very
similarly to what we've already done. Um
I've used that to deploy several apps
before. Um but you should be able to
navigate the rest of these as they all
can generally tie into your GitHub and
grab the code from there. Um so
hopefully that gives you a good overview
of how you deploy. Thanks for joining me
on this course journey and good luck.